Quilt Alliance, Quilters' S.O.S. -- Save Our Stories interviews collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 2: Interviews
  - The Women of Color Quilters Network QSOS
    - Michele David oral history interview conducted by Karen Musgrave, 2009-08-19 (Interview-id OH45069-004)
      - Sound Recordings, 1 digital recording; afc2007009_OH45069_004_05.wav
Cynthia Mumford: MI49016-048
Scott Murkin: NC27205-001
Anita Murphy: QSOS-006
Judy Murrah: QSOS-024
Karen Musgrave: Alliance-03 Alliance-06 AFPBP-38
Jo Ann Musso: QSOS-158
Beth Button Myers: VT05819-DAR020
Paula Nadelstern: QSOS-009
Dorothy M. DePouw Naegele: MI49016-053
Jayne Naff: TX76121-024
Sally Nagode: OK73401-DAR001
Maryanne Nardello: OR97008-OSSDAR54
Dominie Nash: MD-001
Susan Nash: OH43068-005
Shirley Naughton: TX78739-DAR001
Pam Neil: KY40223-001
Johanna Nelson: NC27408-DAR002
Sarah Nephew: QSOS-064
Terrie Newman: QSOS-067
Velda E. Newman: QSOS-010
Carole Nicholas: VA22003-005
Linda Nichols: NC28803-018
Sue Nickels: QSOS-065
Colleen Nickerson: OR97008-OSSDAR08
Joyce B. Nixon: DC20002-006
Nao Nomura: JPN-001 NE68508-001
Ruth Noonan: VA22302-002
Nannie Don Northcutt: TX76121-008
Mitzi Wiebe Oakes: VT05819-014
Marlene O'Bryant-Seabrook: BOQ-045
Barbara Olson: QSOS-091
Maryanne Olson: FL34106-004
Nancy L. Orcutt: VT05819-031
Dorothy Orr: UDel-008
Karen Stiehl Osborn: NE68138-001
Gwen Otte: NE69343-DAR001
Gay Ousley: AFPBP-12
Elizabeth Cherry Owen: ME04553-001
Michelle Owens: OH43040-004
Mabeth Oxenreider: QSOS-096
Juan Pablo: CA95415-17
Hazel Packer: TX76121-047
Maria Padilla: CA95415-07
Connie Page: VT05819-008
Dorothy Palmer: IA50112-006
Karla Palmer: OR97031-002
Nadj Pankey: TX76121-069
Emily Parson: QSOS-115
Barbara Pate: NC28803-020
Charlotte Patera: CA95949-001
Joyce Paterson: CA95482-04
Julie Patterson: NV89407-DAR002
Edna Patterson-Petty: BOQ-008
Beth Payne-Howard: MI49016-040
Marsha Pearson: MO63376-DAR001
Nancy Pearson: QSOS-034
Rachel Pellman: PA17602-001
Andrea Perejda: QSOS-081
Tina Perez: CA95415-16
Mary Perini: AQSG-003
Gina Perkes: AZ85541-001
Cyrena Persons: VT05819-010
Marlene Peterman: QSOS-162
Diane Petersmarck: AFPBP-09
Edna Patterson Petty: IL62201-01
Julia Pfaff: AQATS19119-025
Virginia Todd Phillip: DE03
Sue Pierce: MD20850-002
Kay Piercey: OR97008-OSSDAR10
Vikki Pignatelli: OH43068-001
Ann Dykhuizen Pitcher: NM87111-006
Martha Plager: KY40207-002
Joyce Plants: CO80538-001
Judith Plotner: AQATS19119-007
Lisa Johnson Ponder: OR97008-OSSDAR11
Linda Pool: QSOS-032
Linda Poole: QSOS-022
Yvonne Porcella: Alliance-02 QSOS-011
Lee Porter: DC-001
Ona Porterfield: NM87111-002
Polly Powell: TX76121-015
Pamela Prater: KY41522-012
Ellaree Pray: BOQ-048
Teddy Pruett: AQSG-001
Jean Sadowski Pufpaff: MI49016-018
Louise Quick: NY14722-004
Shawn Quinlan: PA15221-001
Verna Quinlin: IA52659-002
Virginia White Quinn: DC20002-003
Lisa Quintana: OH45373-001
Carolyn Raimy: NY13464-DAR001
Sue Ramey: KY41522-001
Maria Ramirez: CA95415-10
Diana Ramsay: NC28803-004
Barbara Ranck: FL34106-017
Jeanie E. Rash: DE19711-011
Eloise Ratliff: KY41522-002
Gail Rayman: MI49016-036
Peg Reagle: UDel-004
Wen Redmond: BOQ-010
Ann Reed: OR97008-OSSDAR33
Sara Reed: OR97008-OSSDAR32
Suanne Reed: BOQ-034
Wendy Reed: ME04530-001
Leslie Rego: QSOS-169
Jacomina de Regt: VA22204-001
Darlene Reid: AZ85044-010
Sherry Reis: QSOS-146
Sue Reno: Postcard-001
Deborah Repass: DC20005-DAR002
Judy Reubush: VA22801-007
Louise Reynolds: AQSG-008
Ardell Rich: VT05819-DAR018
Leisa Rich: TX75019-001
Dee Richardson: DE19711-006
Emily Richardson: PA19130-001
Penny Rigdon: VA22302-004
Jeri Riggs: QSOS-154
Alice Roberts: NH03773-001
Keisha Roberts: NC27607-001
Miriam Nathan Roberts: QSOS-058
Judith Robinette: IA52659-001
Alice Robinson: TX76121-003
Jackie Robinson: QSOS-106
Lynn Robinson: CA95051-DAR002
Anne Rolfe: MI49016-005
Margaret Rolfe: QSOS-097
Teresa Romano: OH43040-005
Winifred Rombaugh: MI49016-032
Dee Rose: TX76121-067
Anita "Billie" Rosendahl: IA51360-DAR002
June Ross: SC29440-DAR001
Lonni Rossi: AQATS19119-014
Diana Rothe: OR97008-OSSDAR39
Shirley Roubinek: FL34106-003
Lorraine Roy: CANL9H4X4-001
Pam RuBert: AQATS19119-032
Ginny Ruhe: MA01749-004
Paulette Runyon: KY41522-009
Joyce S. Rupp: MI49016-020
Adina Dell Yewell Russell: VA22302-005
Mary Clare Ryan: MA01749-005
Mary Klett Ryan: VT05819-011
Audrey Sacharkiewicz: MA01749-003
JoAnn Sadler: IA51101-007
Priscilla Sage: IA50112-007
Helen Sager: NY14722-007
Evelyn Evatt Salinger: VA22302-007
Juanita Salvador-Burris: IL60608-006
Pauline Salzman: QSOS-076
Juan Sanchez: CA95415-12
Luis Sanchez: CA95415-13
Paola Sanchez: CA95415-14
Arturo Alonzo Sandoval: KY40205-005
Suzanne Sanger: FL34106-002
Janet-Lee Santeusanio: NH03844-001
Edwinna Rush Saucier: NM87111-011
John Sauls: QSOS-168
Ferne Sayre: CA92620-001
Kris Sazaki: BOQ-022
Meena Schaldenbrand: AFPBP-29
Sharon Schamber: FL34106-016
Mary Schilke: VT05819-019
Valli Schiller: IL60564-001
Amanda Schlatre: QSOS-109
Dianne Schlotman: IA51101-009
Linda Schmidt: CA94568-001
Beatrice Schmidtzinsky: TX76121-001
Maribeth Schmit: WI53012-001
Allene Schnaiter: TX78739-DAR002
Barbara Schneider: IL60098-001
Sally Schneider: QSOS-126
Karla Schreffer: BOQ-051
Judy Schryver: NY13021-OCDAR001
Deenie Schuchert: IA51360-DAR001
Pam Schultz: MI49016-047
Joan Schulze: CA94107-001
Deborah Schwartzman: AQATS19119-016
Wilsene Scott: VA22801-002
Angeles Segura: CA95415-04
Rebekka Seigel: KY40205-003
Zora Selliken: CA90505-DAR001
Lee Serrie: CA95415-05
Jonathan Shannon: QSOS-040
Judy Shapiro: MD20816-004A MD20816-004B
Pauline Shaw: CT06060DAR-001
Betty Shea: FL34106-019
Muriel Shea: NE68850-001
Jean Shear: MI49016-006
Maria Shell: AK99516-001 BOQ-038
Theresa Shellcroft: BOQ-006
Shirley Johnston Shelly: VA22302-011
Susan Shie: BOQ-003 OH44691-001
Sherry Shine: BOQ-009
Ethel Shulam: QSOS-166
Pam Shuster: TX77063-001
Debbie Sieling: AZ85225-001
Elly Sienkiewicz: QSOS-014
Julie Silber: IL60601-02
Merry Silber: IL60601-01
Mariann Simmons: VA22801-009
Ami Simms: AFPBP-10 QSOS-159
Mary Sue Simpson: TX76121-010
Mildred Simpson: NY14722-001A NY14722-001B
Carol Ann Sinnreich: OK73507-001
Penny Sisto: IN47119-001
Zylpha Siudara: NY14543-001
Arle Sklar-Weinstein: AQATS19119-022
Shirley Skov: OR97008-OSSDAR18
Jane Slack: OR97008-OSSDAR06
Duncan Slade: ME04556-001
Dicie Sloan: KY41522-008
Sharon Smaldone: FL34106-007
Amy Tetlow Smith: UDel-001
Bonnie Smith: BOQ-004
Emma Jean Smith: OR97008-OSSDAR20
Ginny Smith: AQATS19119-008
Lori Smith: MI49016-038
Louisa L. Smith: BOQ-050 WI53719-001
Lura Schwarz Smith: QSOS-020
Nancy Smith: UDel-002
Nell Denman Smith: QSOS-023
Nettie Smith: CO80503-002
Thelma Smith: AZ85614-001
Barton Snedaker: NY13185-DAR001
Esther Snetz: OH43465-DAR001
Carol Soderlund: QSOS-138
Karen Soma: WA-002
Sharon Somers: IA50112-005
Alice Sommerville: IL60137-001
Kay Sorensen: WI53168-001
Mary Sorenson: QSOS-143
Unis Engle Southwell: MI48824-004
Mimi Sparks: DE20
Estella Spates: MI49016-009
Sara Jane Spaulding: DE19
Joy C. Spence: CA95051-DAR001
Virginia Spiegel: IL61010-001
Shyrlee Stanley: TX76121-029
Dorothy Stapleton: QSOS-104
Lucy Staton: OK74361-DAR001
Suzanne Staud: Alliance-01
Diana Steinhouse: FL34106-005
Mandy Stephens: VA22302-014
Barbara Stewart: QSOS-069
Kathy Stewart: KY41522-010
Lillian Eaton Stewart: OR97008-OSSDAR51
Lisa Shepard Stewart: BOQ-015
Mary Stewart: IL61614-DAR001
Sue Stiner: DE19711-001
Ruth Hamlin Stokes: DC20002-021
Linda Stoltzfus: PA17302-001a PA17302-001b
Mary Stori: AFPBP-18
Norma Storm: MI49016-007
Ted Storm van Weelden: QSOS-113
Dorothea Stratton: IA50036-DAR001
Carol Strauss: QSOS-087
Annie Strivers: DC20002-011
Judy Stryker: VA-003
Betty Ekern Suiter: QSOS-044
Moira Sullivan: QSOS-037
Selena Sullivan: NC27707-001
Lida Croteau Surridge: VT05819-005
Shellen Suttles: IL60640-005
Gabrielle Swain: AQATS19119-003 QSOS-084
Raelaine Swanner: DE01
June Harman Swartzle: MI49016-029
Janette Swecker: WA98198-WSSDAR002
Gerry Sweem: QSOS-026
Barbara Swinea: NC28803-001
Rosemary Switzer: TX76121-061
Judy Szumlas: AFPBP-11
Ellie Taesali: CA95415-35
Sibyl Tarbell: FL33904-001
Carol Taylor: AQATS19119-002
Daphne Taylor: AQATS19119-027
Jessie Taylor: KY41522-006
Pauline Taylor: VT05819-028
Emily Temple: GA30643-DAR001
Nancy Terjesen: FL34285-DAR001
Melanie Testa: TX77010-004
Doris Thackrah: DE19711-013
Brenda Thiems: IL62246-DAR002
Judith Thomas: VT05819-030
Linda Sue Thomas: TX78411-DAR001
Tangie Thomas: OH43040-007
Jean Thompson: TX76121-014
Jeanette Thompson: BOQ-005
Zena Thorpe: QSOS-018 QSOS-129
Joann Threet: KY40359-DAR001
Richard Tims: TX76308-001
Ricky Tims: QSOS-080
Mary Ellen Tjossen: IA51046-01
Margaret B. Todd: VA20783-001
Teri Henderson Tope: OH43212-005
Maria Tortolero: IL60608-005
Micki Towell: OR97008-OSSDAR23
Donna Allen Townsley: OR97008-OSSDAR35 OR97008-OSSDAR44
Judith Trager: CO80504-001
Beverly Ann Treneman: OR97008-OSSDAR16
Lali Tsetskhladze: GEO-007
Betty Tucker: RI02852-001
Susan Turnquist: QSOS-142
Priscilla Tyson: FL34451-DAR001
Linda Uldriks: MI49016-023
June Underwood: AQATS19119-009
Julie John Upshaw: QSOS-136
Pam Upward: TX76121-059
Bette Uscott-Wooley: AQATS19119-018
Carmela Valdivia: CA95415-33
Jean Van Bockel: ID83801-DAR001
Ingrid Van Hengel: ME04105-001
Larkin Van Horn: QSOS-117
Henk Van Kooten: QSOS-148
Carolyn Lee Vehslage: AQATS19119-017
Meiny Vermaas-van der Heide: QSOS-156
Cindy Verrill: ME04038-001
Lita Verts: OR97008-OSSDAR53
Marie Villanueva: CA95620-001
Jean Vining: TX76121-002
Barb Vlack: PAQ-001
Petra Voegtle: DEU-001
Elsie Vredenburg: MI48824-005
Kellie Wachter: HI98617-DAR003
Dale Waddle: MI49016-024
Evelyn Wade: NM87111-007
Susan Walen: BOQ-001
David Walker: OH44140-03
Leslie Walker: IA51101-005
Mary Walter: MA01749-006
Millie Wark: MA01535-001
Elizabeth Warner: BOQ-031
Wanda Warner: MI49016-022
Ruth Warren: DE02
Carmel Washington: DC20002-008
Cookie Washington: BOQ-020
Mary V. Washington: DC20002-017
Laura Wasilowski: GA30188-003 QSOS-047
Karen Watts: Alliance-09
Mary Weathers: TX76121-071
Kathy Weaver: AQATS19119-005
Dixie Webb: AQSG-010
Dorothy Weeks: MI49016-015
Joanne Weis: KY40207-007
Diane Wendorf: ME04073-001
Alma Wenger: VA22801-006
Helen West: TX76121-009
Barbara Wester: IL60540-001
Marcia Wethli: NY14722-006
Norma Wetzell: OR97008-OSSDAR19
Rachel Wetzler: OH43068-002
Catherine Whalen: CT06511-001
Frances (Sue) Whitaker: DE19711-005
David White: CO80922-001 CO80922-002 CO80922-003
Kathyanne White: AQATS19119-028
Valerie White: BOQ-014 KY40205-004
Valerie White: KY40205-004
Judy Whitson: AL35405-DAR001
Maggy Wilcox: OR97008-OSSDAR49
Carol Wilcoxen: DE19711-009
Jan Wildman: QSOS-085
Eleanor Wilkinson: MI49016-019
Barbara Williams: MI49016-043
Jan Williams: TX76121-039
Rita Williams: NC28803-023
Roberta Williams: WI53209-001
Sondra Williams: TX76121-025
Judith Williamson: MI49016-004
Beth Wilson: IA51046-02
Olive Wilson: IA51046-03
Shirley Wilson: MI49016-027
Mary Ellen Winborn: TX75225-DAR001
Katie Winchell: NC28803-012
Roger Winchell: NC28803-019
Cindy Wismann: FL34106-020
Mildred Wittig: VA22801-004
Pauline Wolff: MI48824-001
Mary Wollenhaupt: CO80212-002
Sandra Woock: MD20817-001
Kaye Wood: QSOS-099
Margaret Wood: AZ85016-001
Sherri Lynn Wood: CA94130-001
Marilyn Woodin: AQSG-009
Gail Reid Woodruff: IN47421-001
Phyllis Jean Wooten: TX76121-057
Jeanne Wright: ME04062-DAR001
Charles Wunderlich: TX76121-017
Pang Xiong Sirirathasuk Sikoun: PH-01
Houa Yang: PH-03
Kathleen Yaw: NY14722-002
Juanita Yeager: KY40207-003
Arveda Jean Yeo: MI49016-058
Ede Yeomans: FL34106-011
Rebecca Yoder: IL60640-001
Adrienne Yorinks: NY-001
Janie York: AQSG-013
Aloyse Yorko: FL34106-001
Blanche Young: QSOS-112
Helen Frost Young: QSOS-110
Iris Young: TX76121-027
Cyndi Zacheis Souder: VA22003-002
Sauda Zahra: BOQ-042
Margret Zalfen: DEU-002
Rosemary Zaugg: TX76121-058
Diana Ziegler: DE19963-003
Madge Ziegler: DE12
Elaine Zinn: NC28803-006
Elva Zoltai: FL34106-009
Barbara Zygiel: VA22302-008
Appendix B: Interviewer Index
Alphabetical list of interviewers.
Hester Able
Janelle Acher
Gloria Adriance-Answell
Karen Alexander
Marilyn Altman
Sally Ambrose
Gloria Answell
Helen Aponte
Janelle Archer
Ann Atkinson
Mimi Ayars
Margaret Bader
Margaret Bader
Linda Baker
Jeri Baldwin
Cathy Ball
Debbie Ballard
Fran Ballard
Kristen Bara
Linda Lemons Bardell
Linda Barton
Karen G. Bauer
Misty Beatty
Barbara Beck
Erma Beeson
Norma L. Belt
Karen Bennick
Theresa Boock
Margaret Bordelon
Paula Bosselman
Sue Bowman
Linda Brammer
Alessandra Bravo
Mary Bulsfordes
Sylvia Burke
Dorothy Burleigh
Nancy Burton
Sandra Button
Leah Call
Frances Carlton
Catherine Carrara
Karolyn Christopher
Pam Clark
Martha Class
Carol Clemens
Betty Colburn
Ruth Cole
Ronda Coleman
Bernice Cowan
Meg Cox
Patricia Crews
Dorothy Crooks
Nancy Currier
Melissa Danielsson
Elizabeth Davis
Jodie Davis
Lenna DeMarco
Violette Denney
Karen Dennis
Ruth Duncan
Megan Dwyre
Cathy Eckbreth
Nancy Edwards
Janell Epp
Tomme Fent
Marcie Ferris
Darlene Fiske
Nola Forbes
Lynn Forster
Jan Frank
Judy Frisch
Jayne Garver
Joanne Gasperik
Marilyn Geary
Beverly Gentry
Heather Gibson
Sue Glen
Flavin Glover
Joann Kensler Gordon
Nikki Green
Diane Greene
Jo Frances Greenlaw
Maxine Grothouse
Rachel Grove
Kathy Hall
Frieda Hardee
Phyllis J. Harris
Genevieve Hassan
Bonnie Koski Hawes
Jana Hawley
Alice Helms
Amy Henderson
Bernard Herman
Melva Hightower
Judy Holley
Lorna Holloway
Diane Hom
Ellen Hopkins
Ellen Hopkins
Mary Ellen Hopkins
Brenda Horton
Jean Howell
Sally Hudspeth
Geri Jackson
Lorraine Jackson
Renee Jackson
Christy Johnson
Elaine Johnson
Joyce Starr Johnson
Julee Casey Johnson
Kathy Johnson
Edie Jones
Kay Jones
Liz Jones
Patricia Keller
Mary Lois Kelley
Joan Kennedy
Joyce Kilmer
Michele Kinney
Lynn Kinsell
Marylynn Kleeman
Kate Kleinert
Carol Klopfenstein
Eva Knight
Carolyn Kolzow
Kathryn Koos-Lee
Joe Koval
Judy Koybal
Susie Krage
Jane Kucko
Paulette Lancaster
Mary Laskowski
Evelyn Laughman
Bill Ledford
Colleen Lemkuil
Judy Linn
Angela Lodin
Isabelle Long
Jean Look-Krischano
SharonAnn Louden
SharonAnn Louden
Kelli Lucas
Margie Laws Luke
Charletta MacDougal
Carolyn Malaski
Terry Maloney
Marlene McDerment
Charletta McDougall
Suzanne Hill McDowell
Janice K. McGraw
Janet McManus
Sandy Mehall
Ellen Menefee
Susan Metzger
Donna Mikesch
Lori Miller
Roberta Mills
Amy Milne
Joan Minde-Welch
Linda Moore
Pat Morgan
Zipra Morgan
Allison Moss
Karen Musgrave
Terri Newman
Kathryn Z. Nicodemus
Nedra Gilmore Nitcher
Patricia Otis
Dee Paul
Judy Pelston
Kimber Pepper
Joyce Peters
Julie Pittmann
Clarisse Pitto
Karen Plummer
Patricia Plunk
Lisa Ponder
Carol Porter
JoAnn Pospisil
Judy Preston
Jennifer Pretty
Frances Price
Jennifer Priddy
Gayle Pritchard
Vicki Quint
Diana Ramsay
Darlene Reid
Dee Richardson
Claire Lynn Robinson
Judith-Ann Saks Rosenthal
Sharon Ross
Le Rowell
Judy Roybal
Sarah Ruhlan
Joyce Rupp
Jean Rusk
Susan Russ
JoAnn Russo
Evelyn Salinger
Pauline Salzman
Virginia Sanders
Suzanne Sanger
Pam Schultz
Linda Hardin Sehrt
Patricia Shaer
Midge Shaw
Ann Shibut
Cary Shields
Janice Simpson
Amy Tetlow Smith
David Smith
Janneken Smucker
James Snetz
Martha Spark
Estella Spates
Joy Combs Spence
Mary Jane Springman
Joyce Starr Johnson
Karen Stewart
Susan Stiner
Debbie Strickland
Judy Stryker
Karen Taylor
Emily Temple
Jackie Theriot
Marsha Turner
Christy Velasco
Elaine Ventre
Theresa Thompkins Walsh
Sara Walvoord
Sally Wasson
Betty Jean Weaver
Dixie Webb
Catherine Whalen
Eleanor Wilkinson
Sondra Williams
Betty Wilson
Marietta M. Womack
Mary Worrall
Jeanne Wright
Georgeann Wrinkle
Janie York